<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">San Jerónimo Travel 2.0</string>

    <string name="title_activity_hotel">HOTELS</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bar">BARES</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tour">TOURIST SITES</string>
    <string name="title_activity_town">SAN JERÓNIMO...</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About us...</string>

    <string name="about">
        <biu>SAN JERÓNIMO TRAVEL</biu> \n
        Apps mobile devices \n
        <b>University of Antioquia</b> \n
        <u>Developed by:</u>
        <i>Gerson Cárdenas</i>
    </string>

    <string name="title_quimbaya">Quimbaya Hotel</string>
    <string name="title_eltesoro">El Tesoro Hotel</string>
    <string name="title_dharma">Dharma Hotel</string>

    <string name="text_quimbaya">The Quimbaya Hotel is a Country Resort located at San
        Jerónimo Antioquia.  A place of great natural exuberance and tropical climate.
        An excellent choice to satisfy your needs for rest, recreation, conventions and meetings.\n
        <b>Direction: El Rincón countryside. Km 1, San Jerónimo, Antioquia \n
        Phone number: (4) 2684915</b>
    </string>

    <string name="text_eltesoro">El Tesoro Hotel and Convention Center is ideal for a
        family getaway,the natural surroundings, tranquility and all amenities you need to
        feel the guest more pampered and enjoy an excellent stay.\n
        <b>Direction: road to Santa Fé de Antioquia, San Jerónimo, Antioquia \n
        Phone number: (4) 8582054</b>
    </string>

    <string name="text_dharma">Dharma Hotel Boutique Spa, a hotel for your senses.
        We offer a wide range of services to meet the least of your desires.
        Come and live an unforgettable experience in the best hotel at San Jeronimo.\n
        <b>Direction: 1 mile, old road towards Sopetrán, San Jerónimo, Antioquia \n
        Phone number: (4) 8581779 / 3205127705</b>
    </string>

    <string name="title_route62">Route62 Bar</string>
    <string name="title_tonunu">Tonunu Bar</string>

    <string name="text_route62">Route 62, Bar and Grills. \n Excellent attention.\n
        <b>Direction: Route 62, San Jerónimo, Antioquia \n
        Phone number: 311 5205958</b>
    </string>

    <string name="text_tonunu">Disco Bar Tonunu, the best  Crossover place of San Jerónimo,
        where we have the best prices on local and imported liquors.
        Excellent attention.\n
        <b>Direction: Avenue 11 # 23 - 00, San Jerónimo, Antioquia \n
        Phone number: (4) 8580331</b>
    </string>

    <string name="title_tamarindos">Los Tamarindos Park</string>
    <string name="title_guaracu">Quebrada Guaracú</string>
    <string name="title_lacandelaria">Nuestra Señora de La Candelaria Church</string>

    <string name="text_tamarindos">Located in San Jerónimo, near the exit of the West tunnel,
        this park offers an excellent alternative for fun, wetlands, children, family and
        semi-Olympic swimming pool; sports courts, four spectacular waterslides, lazy river rides,
        self-service, gym, reading room, internet and a large auditorium for 350 people are
        always available for the enjoyment of visitors and businesses.\n
        <b>Direction: San Jerónimo, Km 32 - 33 road to the sea \n
        Phone number: 57(4) 858 04 75\n
        Website: www.comfenalcoantioquia.com</b>
    </string>

    <string name="text_guaracu">Near the city center only 30 minutes walking is The Guaracú creek,
        whose waters flow down from the top of the ridge and dramatically get close passing
        through San Jerónimo forming what is known in the region as "Las Angusturas" and consist in
        narrow channels that the creek has carved its way through the rocks.
    </string>

    <string name="text_lacandelaria">The church is a neoclassical style, was built between
        1864-1895, is rectangular, its interior is divided into three naves, the lateral walls are
        made of mud, its main facade is built in solid bricks glued with mortar and where stands
        the bulrush with three openings for the bells.
    </string>

        <string name="text_town">Welcome to the town of San Jeronimo, West of Antioquia, Sun and
            Fruits route, connected to the city of Medellin by one of the greatest engineering works
            in Colombia such as the Tunnel of the West Fernando Gomez Martinez, 35 minutes from
            Medellin.\n\n
        <b>Country: </b> Colombia\n
        <b>State: </b> Antioquia\n
        <b>Region: </b> SouthWest\n
        <b>Location: </b> 35 km west of Medellín\n
        <b>Population: </b> 11.627 citizens \n
        <b>Demonym: </b> Jeronimitas, San Jeronimeños\n
        <b>Website: </b> 	http://www.sanjeronimo-antioquia.gov.co/
    </string>

</resources>